<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Welcome on Rivière Parley Home</title>
    <link>https://rmflight.github.io/rpmain/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Welcome on Rivière Parley Home</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    
	<atom:link href="https://rmflight.github.io/rpmain/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>A Brief History of Human Colonization</title>
      <link>https://rmflight.github.io/rpmain/pages/a-brief-history-of-human-colonization/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rmflight.github.io/rpmain/pages/a-brief-history-of-human-colonization/</guid>
      <description>It is clear that the Ks’ou alien Colonizers functioned as a disruption to the Human historical timeline. Humans, Earth-wide, would never be the same as before the Ks’ou arrived on Earth, and the nature of Ks’ou control would obliterate and disrupt Human-driven possibility. This has never before been made so clear as the introduction of the terms ‘Pre-Ks’ou Era’ (PKE) and ‘Post-Ks’ou Era’ (PsKE) in many Earth-published textbooks; though these terms are charged and used sparingly here, it should be noted that this work before you is written in 39 PsKE.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Constructed Languages</title>
      <link>https://rmflight.github.io/rpmain/pages/constructed-languages/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rmflight.github.io/rpmain/pages/constructed-languages/</guid>
      <description>Constructed languages are crafted by the author, and therefore subject to human error. If you find anything amiss, please let me know!
Ks&amp;rsquo;Sassi (Ks&amp;rsquo;ou language) #  Under construction! Check out the IPA pulmonic consonant chart with audio for sounds. Vowels coming soon.
 Overview #  Ks&amp;rsquo;ou language, translinguated to the human tongue, largely relies on surdic consonants (uttered with the breath and not sound -(f, k, p, s, t), voiced plosives (d, g, b), and a few vowels (the most common are a, i, e).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bibliography</title>
      <link>https://rmflight.github.io/rpmain/pages/bibliography/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rmflight.github.io/rpmain/pages/bibliography/</guid>
      <description>Coming soon, but here are some of the people that have been featured in the novel so far:
 James Baldwin Frantz Fanon Hortense Spillers Ngũgĩ wa Thiong&amp;rsquo;o  Colonial References (warning: some links have graphic images) #    The Parsley Massacre  Hagåtña  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact &amp; Acknowledgements</title>
      <link>https://rmflight.github.io/rpmain/pages/contact-and-acknowledgements/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rmflight.github.io/rpmain/pages/contact-and-acknowledgements/</guid>
      <description>First, Thank You. #  I give gratitude to Leilani Serafin, my avid reader who has offered insights and advice beyond my imagination. It takes a remarkable person to find an editor who &amp;ldquo;gets you,&amp;rdquo; but also offers critical feedback that refines you.
Who am I? #  Rivière Parley is the pseudonym for a professor of Literature, Language, and Pedagogy somewhere on kyôsta l-Earth (also known as elu-sthii) Earth. Much of the content of the Symbiosis Series, whether direct or not, is informed by the horrors of her dissertation, which (broadly) addresses African colonization, race, identity politics, and (socio)linguistics.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>